Shaik Sirabanu

Mobile: +91 7989984667 Email: sb.shaik17@gmail.com

Objectives

To seek an opportunity in a challenging environment, in an aggressive company, where I can bring the best out of me and expand my horizons on my technical background and experience. Zeal to accept work related challenges, dedication towards work.

Executive Summary

Having 6+ years of experience as Accountant in Banking Sector & IT sector.

Organizing books and maintaining inventory records.

Track & supervise the petty cash.

Preparation of monthly, quarterly and annual closing statements and reports Substantiates financial transactions by auditing documents.

Analyze financial information (e.g. revenues, expenditures and cash management) to ensure all operations are within budget.

Responsible for timely monthly consolidated financial statements, payments, cash-flow management reporting.

Experience Summary

Segra Infoware Private Limited, Hyderabad, India

Worked as Accountant from Feb 2017 to June 2023

ICICI Bank, Hyderabad, India

Worked in Credit Cards verification department from Aug 2015 to Jan 2017

IBS Infolabs, Hyderabad, India

Worked as Jr. Accountant from Apr 2013 to Jul 2015

Education

M.B.A Finance from Institute of Aeronautical Engineering & Technology in 2012

M.Com from Acharya Nagarjuna University in 2008.

B. Com from Acharya Nagarjuna University in 2005.

Technical Skills

ERP: Tally 9, SAP Financials
Operating Systems: Windows 7, Windows 10

Packages: MS Office (Excel, Word and Power Point)

Roles and Responsibilities

Segra Infoware Private Limited

From Feb 2017 to June 2023

Position: Accountant

Responsibilities:

- o Employee Salaries preparation and pay slip generations.
- o Coordinating with the Clients and monitoring.
- Day to Day Receipts and Payments.
- Should be able to calculate future cash flows fairly accurately
- Post Invoice documentation.
- O Preparation of Income & Expenditure statement.
- Preparation of Profit & Loss A/c.
- Reconciliation and analysis of GL accounts.
- Management financial reports generation (Monthly, Quarterly and yearly)
- IT filing and responding required documents for Auditors.

ICICI Bank Private Limited

From Aug 2015 to Jan 2017

Position: Accountant

Responsibilities:

- Processing of retail and corporate cc applications.
- o Checking of CIBIL, CPCS, DEDUPE, FI reports & KYC details validation
- o Preparation of final reports the customer income statement
- o Preparation of FIR SHEETS to the customer
- Verification of complete customer details.
- Enhancement of credit limit requests to customer.

IBS Infolabs

From Apr 2013 to Jul 2015

Position: Jr. Store Accountant

Responsibilities:

- Accounting of day to day business transactions
- Updating of material inward and out register
- Preparing GRIR (Goods Received Cum Inspection Report)
- Preparing stock statement every month and sending reports
- Preparation of Purchase requisitions
- Accounting of purchase, expenses bills and releasing the payments to vendors as per Terms of Payment
- Invoice Verification with Purchase Order